this is a photo of a film ceramic coil
enlarged thousands of times as you can
see there are millions of micron sized
pores in the ceramic cube the key
component of the electronic atomizer is
composed of a porous ceramic substrate
and a thin layer of metallic film in
this video we will explore the secrets
of ceramic coils and talk with the
scientist since more research institute
in san shed the world leading
atomization technology company and
manufacturer ceramic atomization
technology what are the hidden secrets
ceramics is not the only material used
in coil design glass fiber organic
cotton metallic mesh and other materials
all have been widely adopted the ceramic
material used in coils is different from
that on our dinner table it is
engineered porous micro structures with
special compositions the raw materials
used in film are processed minerals from
nature after special high temperatures
centering processes interconnected micro
pores are formed inside the pore size is
about one-fifth of a human hair these
micro pores play a vital role in
conducting and locking the e-liquid
inside the substrate during vaporization
[Music]
thanks to the surface tension and
capillary action the e-liquid confirm e8
through the substrate and absorb on the
surface the porous ceramic is both
strong absorb ability and biological
compatibility similar as activated
carbons which are widely used in many
household appliances such as water
filters refrigerator deodorants facial
masks and toothpaste etc the advanced
ceramic atomizers are designed based on
rigorous Sciences and assembled in
medical grade environment they are the
next generation products for safer
atomization applications the heating and
vaporization temperature of the coils
has a direct impact on the vaping
experience the field coils are composed
of a ceramic substrate and a layer of
metallic film the ceramic is centered at
a high temperature and formed into the
shape of a bowl the metallic film is
printed onto the substrate surface with
a s shape in order to provide efficient
and even heating just like stove and pod
and cooking the atomizer vaporizes the
e-liquid into vapor while heated by the
metallic film with precise temperature
compared to other materials such as
fiber and cotton the film coil is
special in its physical structure
material property and industrial design
these combinations contribute to faster
rise in temperature and even temperature
distribution on the substrate surface
the precise temperature control enabled
by the film can greatly reduce the
amount of aldehydes and ketones produced
during the vaporization
[Music]
another advantage of film is the even
heating can effectively eliminate most
of the partial carbonation and reduce
the burnt taste problem ceramic
atomizers with proper design can not
only deliver a better vaping experience
for end users but also be applied in
other fields accurate atomization
enables the effective ingredients in the
liquid to be reproduced in the vapor and
assimilated more effectively
atomization technology has been used in
medical applications for long such as
orally inhaled drugs for treatment of
seasonal asthma the size of particles
produced in regular atomization can vary
greatly particles smaller than 2.5 um
can be readily deposited in the human
respiratory tract in oral cavity and
those smaller than one um can be
absorbed by the lung the aerosol
particles produced by film ceramic oil
are smaller than one um which lead to
better lung absorption more intense
flavors and greater satisfaction smore
Research Institute is partnering with
multiple national and global research
organizations to explore product
applications of the film technology and
medical and healthcare field
in summary electronic atomizer is not
the only application of ceramic oil with
more fundamental research and
development of next generation advanced
atomization technology more product
applications of ceramic atomizer may be
expected and soon become part of our
daily life
you
[Music]